dukecareers.com 2010-10-01

# Privacy Policy - Duke Careers

Privacy Statement

Overview 

People Wise Software Ltd. d.b.a AutomotiveJobFinder.com is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site. By creating an account on the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement.

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in Canada. If you access the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site from the United States, your usage of the site constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of the United States to Canada.

Our sites contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. AutomotiveJobFinder.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information we collect on the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site, and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion. 

Collection and Retention of Information 

In order to provide you with the services of AutomotiveJobFinder.com, in some areas of our Web site, AutomotiveJobFinder.com requests or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number credit card number, (if applicable), contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In order to continually enhance your use of AutomotiveJobFinder.com and to provide you requested information about AutomotiveJobFinder.com third party partners, in other areas, AutomotiveJobFinder.com may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your postal code, preferences, interests and favorites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. Examples of areas on the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site where we collect personal or combined personal and demographic data are pages where you can open an AutomotiveJobFinder.com account, sign up to use a service, post a resume, or enter a contest. 

In addition, AutomotiveJobFinder.com may indirectly collect information about you when you use certain third party services on our Web site. Such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in additional services offered by our third party partners. 

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our site, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by AutomotiveJobFinder.com. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used to evaluate different aspects of the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web Site. The information may also be used for site security and law enforcement purposes.

AutomotiveJobFinder.com may sometimes afford you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioral, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services.

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of AutomotiveJobFinder.com, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom AutomotiveJobFinder.com has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of AutomotiveJobFinder.com. 

Since we believe that managing your career is an on-going process, your job application history is retained by AutomotiveJobFinder.com for eighteen (12) months. Of course, you can correct or update your AutomotiveJobFinder.com account profile and resume at any time. Moreover, you can delete your resume from our online database or close your AutomotiveJobFinder.com account at any time, in which event we will remove all our copies of your resume and AutomotiveJobFinder.com account profile information. 

Use of Information by AutomotiveJobFinder.com

We use the information we gather on the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site, creating a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. 

We may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from AutomotiveJobFinder.com or its affiliated companies or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. (The term "affiliated companies" is defined in the section of this Statement entitled "Contact Information.") 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the AutomotiveJobFinder.com site, such as new AutomotiveJobFinder.com opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. 

We have an area where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in this area becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or to contact you for further information. 

Disclosure of Information to Others 

We do not disclose to third parties your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site (such as the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth in the following four subparagraphs. 

  * We may disclose such information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you indicate that you would like to receive information about the products or services of third parties at the time you register for an AutomotiveJobFinder account, we may supply your contact information to third parties such as employers, recruiters, data aggregators, marketers or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. We may use data we have about you (such as the interests and preferences you have expressed) to determine whether you might be interested in the products or services of a particular third-party. 
  * We may disclose such information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 
  * We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of AutomotiveJobFinder.com or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
  * We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of AutomotiveJobFinder.com's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event AutomotiveJobFinder.com becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, AutomotiveJobFinder.com or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court.

AutomotiveJobFinder.com may also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to its Web site with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors that visit AutomotiveJobFinder.com's site and how those visitors use the site. 

Information gathered on a page in a career site hosting recruitment area, or on a co-branded page (such as that of a contest co-sponsored by AutomotiveJobFinder.com and another company), may become the property of the other company or of both AutomotiveJobFinder.com and the other company. In that instance, the use of such information by the other company may be subject to the privacy policy of that company and, in any event, AutomotiveJobFinder.com is not responsible for that company's use of your personal or demographic information.

Resumes 

Since AutomotiveJobFinder.com is a career site, we give you the option of putting your resume in our database. There are two ways of doing this: 

  * 1\. You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product. 
  * If you allow your resume to be searchable, then all parties with access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) will have access to your resume. 

In addition, you can also elect to make your resume confidential which means that your contact info and current employer will be not be displayed to all parties with access to our searchable resume database. 

We attempt to limit access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) only to paying employers, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in our searchable database. You may remove your resume from our database at any time. However, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to that database or to obtain a copy of that database, as well as parties who have otherwise gained access to the database, may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes in these instances. 

Use of Cookies 

AutomotiveJobFinder.com uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize AutomotiveJobFinder.com pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to the AutomotiveJobFinder.com site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing.

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site. 

Use of Web Beacons 

AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information on AutomotiveJobFinder.com; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage 

Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides.

Updating Your Information 

You have the right to demand that your personal information be deleted from AutomotiveJobFinder.com. You may review, correct, update or change your AutomotiveJobFinder.com account profile information at any time by simply logging into your AutomotiveJobFinder.com account, going to your Account Profile, and editing it with the options provided to log in to your account. You may review, delete, correct, update or change your resume on AutomotiveJobFinder.com at any time by simply logging into your AutomotiveJobFinder.com account, going to Manage resumes, and deleting it or editing it with the options provided. You can request that your AutomotiveJobFinder.com account be deleted by contacting AutomotiveJobFinder.com at [info@automotivejobfinder.com](mailto:info@automotivejobfinder.com "info@automotivejobfinder.com")

If you opted to receive newsletters, commercial e-mails or other communications from AutomotiveJobFinder.com or third parties at the time you registered with AutomotiveJobFinder.com, but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out by editing your Account Profile as described above. If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by editing your Account Profile. 

Security

AutomotiveJobFinder.com has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

When you place an order online at AutomotiveJobFinder.com, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. AutomotiveJobFinder.com uses a service company to process its credit card transactions. 

Children 

AutomotiveJobFinder.com is not intended for children under 15 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 15. 

Contact Information 

AutomotiveJobFinder.com is a name under which Peoplewise Software Ltd., with its principal place of business 220 A Dogwood Drive, Ladysmith, BC, Canada, V9G 1T2 and certain of its affiliated companies do business. ("Affiliated companies" means entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with Peoplewise Software Ltd.,). Peoplewise Software Ltd. is the legal entity which determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site. The information we gather on the AutomotiveJobFinder.com Web site may be shared within Peoplewise Software Ltd. and its affiliated companies. 

We welcome your comments concerning this Privacy Statement. 

Thank you for using AutomotiveJobFinder.com
